You know what? If we kill 4,000 Palestinian kids, you know what? It wasn't enough. It wasn't enough.
Go, go, go, go.
It's not my fault that you pray to a criminal.
Listen, listen, I'm working now, okay? Can you leave, please? Go, please.
You're not working. There's nobody here.
I'm just working here. Yeah, go.
There's nobody here. I'm going to put big signs here that say this guy believes in Hamas.
You want to buy something?
No, I don't.
Okay, why sit here?
I won't give you a penny of my money.
Listen, listen, why sit here?
What?
You want to buy something?
No.
Okay, go.
I don't want to go. I have a right to stand here.
You have no right to be on the sidewalk.
Do you have a permit?
Yeah, I have a permit. I have a license.
Okay, but you don't have a visa.
I have a visa for my friend. Go.
What do you have?
It's not your business. Go.
No, it is my business because I actually know the guy who owns all these...
I have an American citizen. Do you have it?
You're an American citizen?
Yeah, I have it.
How? How did you become an American citizen?
It's not your business. Go.
No, you're right.
I'm born here.
But you're a terrorist.
You support terrorism.
Listen, go. I'm not supporting something.
You do. You support terrorism.
I'm not...
Go. I'm just working here.
You're a terrible person.
You kill children, not me.
What?
Go.
My kids? What about my kids?
You kill children, not me. Go.
I didn't kill children.
Okay, why sit here?
You know what?
If we killed 4,000 Palestinian kids, you know what?
It wasn't enough.
Go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
Go.
Go, go.